# Naritchaya Louis

(440) 990-7233 | naritchayalouis@gmail.com | Nashville, TN, 37221 | linkedin.com/in/naritchaya-louis-17786a8b | https://github.com/NKLouis | https://nklouis.github.io/Portfolio/

#### **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Web Developer leveraging a background in the medical, education, and research fields. Excellent interpersonal communication, a strong attention to detail, accurate documentation, good decision making and problem solving. Recognized for a customer-service focus and the ability to treat both internal and external customers with compassion at all times.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Node.Js, Express, JavaScript, jQuery, React.js, React, JSX, GIT, GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Mongoose, Handlebars, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Materialize, APIs, Heroku, Terminal, AJAX, Restful API, ES6, React Hooks, JSON, Sequelize

#### RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Burger | Front End Developer | Deployed Link: <a href="https://whispering-bayou-29942.herokuapp.com/">https://whispering-bayou-29942.herokuapp.com/</a> | Github Link: <a href="https://github.com/NKLouis/burger">https://github.com/NKLouis/burger</a>

Burger is a restaurant app that lets users input the names of burgers they'd like to eat.

- Role: Created HTML page styled with CSS to be able to add burgers to devour. Made a MySQL database to store
  and change data and set up the Express server to request the use of the built-in Express file from Node
  modules.
- Tools Utilized: MySQL, NodeJs, Express, Handlebars, Javascript, Heroku, Bootstrap, HTML and CSS

Friend Finder | Front End Developer | Deployed Link: <a href="https://friendfinderappthatiscool.herokuapp.com/">https://friendfinderappthatiscool.herokuapp.com/</a> | Github Link: <a href="https://github.com/NKLouis/groupFinder">https://github.com/NKLouis/groupFinder</a>

Burger is a restaurant app that lets users input the names of burgers they'd like to eat.

- Role: Designed and Styled the pages with React-BS, created models and routes.
- Tools Utilized: BcryptJS, Dotenv, MySQL, Sequelize, React-BS, HTML, React, NodeJS, Axios, Heroku and Express

Note-Taker | Full Stack Developer | Deployed Link: <a href="https://sleepy-hamlet-60722.herokuapp.com/?">https://sleepy-hamlet-60722.herokuapp.com/?</a> | Github Link: <a href="https://github.com/NKLouis/Note-Taker">https://github.com/NKLouis/Note-Taker</a>

Note-Taker is an application that can be used to write, save, and delete notes.

- **Role**: Builded the backend and connect to the frontend which is already created. Created HTML and API routes. Used an Express backend and saved and retrieved note data from a JSON file via routes.
- Tools Utilized: CSS, HTML, Javascript, NodeJS and Heroku

# **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

American Red Cross; Nashville, TN

7/2019 -

# Present

## Component Manufacturing Technician

Successfully operate, maintain, and perform validation and quality control checks on equipment. Ensure adequate inventory of required supplies. Diligently perform data entry and operate the computer programs associated with component production, labeling, storage and sample tube management. Maintain accurate, legible and complete manufacturing department records. Control accurate electronic and physical inventory locations for products/samples.

- Effectively analyze and make decisions based on visual inspection and information provided from other departments to meet time requirements and quality standards. Identify and quarantine products/samples that don't meet quality requirements.
- Collaborate effectively with internal customers, vendors and volunteers allowing for strong business relationships.

#### **EXPERIENCE CONTINUED**

# Saint Matthew Catholic School; Franklin, TN

8/2016-1/2020

# After school Teacher Assistant (formerly YMCA Fun Company)

Provided participants with the appropriate leadership during the program. Develop and plan activities that incorporate program goals into the daily routine. Effectively maintained open communication between after school staff and school personnel.

# Bangkok Market; Nashville, TN

6/2015-08/2016

#### Store Clerk

Provided customer service to consumers on the floor. Greeted customers and guide them in finding products they want to buy. Maintained the outlook of a store by cleaning and restocking shelves.

## Khon Kaen University; Khon Kaen, Thailand

1/2012- 1/2013

# **Graduate Teaching Assistant**

Assisted faculty or other instructional staff in post secondary institutions by performing teaching or teaching-related duties, such as proctors exams, grades tests and homework, and records grades in grade book. Assigned material in class as needed.

## Khon Kaen University; Khon Kaen, Thailand

1/2012- 1/2013

#### Research Assistant

Participated in the design, administration and monitoring of clinical trials. Analyzed and evaluated clinical data gathered during research. Traveled to various sites within a specified geographical area, as appropriate to the objectives of the study.

#### Thai National Cancer Center; Bangkok, Thailand

03/2010-6/2010

# Molecular Epidemiology Intern

Conducted and recorded face-to-face interviews with patients, in accordance with predetermined interview protocol, data collection procedures and documentation standards.

Assisted senior research staff in their tasks and performed tests on equipment and instruments for quality.

## **EDUCATION**

# Full Stack Web Development Certificate - Vanderbilt University; Nashville, TN | 2020

A 24-week intensive boot camp program focused on gaining technical programming and market-driven skills

Master of Public Health (Nutrition for Health)- KhonKaen University; Khon Kaen, Thailand

Bachelor of Science (Biotechnology)- KhonKaen University; Khon Kaen, Thailand